persopo.com 2018-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Persopo People Search

### Persopo Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") discloses how Persopo.com uses the personal information it gathers on this site. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on this website.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will not be able to purchase a subscription to our services. You can also request that we not use any information you submitted by clicking here.

The personal information we collect includes your name, email address, shipping address, and payment information. Other information we collect is clearly labeled at the time of collection. We use your email address and name to create and manage your account. We use your payment information to obtain payment for your subscription. Payment information includes your name, card number, and other information necessary to process the transaction. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

We also use the information that we collect to show you advertising that will often be targeted based upon your online activity. We use your personal information directly, indirectly, and in combination with data we exchange with other parties. We also sell, license, transfer, and share your personal information with our strategic business partners, unaffiliated list brokers, affiliate marketers, and companies that want to advertise other products and services. Once a third-party obtains your personal information, its subsequent use is controlled by the business practices of the third party, which is beyond our control.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, and members of, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. We do not respond to your browser's "do not track" signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information. Also, we permit third parties to collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our website and related services.

We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.

Please be advised that other circumstances may arise that compel us to disclose your personal information. For example, we may be required to disclose information to the government or third parties in connection with court or administrative proceedings. Also, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

This website is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

This website is owned and operated by:

Persopo.com  
848 N. Rainbow Blvd., Suite 20  
Las Vegas, NV 89107

This privacy policy is effective as of February 21st, 2014.

Persopo's goal is to provide easy online access to public record information in a fast, safe, and affordable manner. Because Persopo is not a Consumer Reporting Agency as defined by the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA), you must not use this site if you are searching for a person because you are considering them for employment, credit or insurance eligibility, tenancy, or any other reason that would require FCRA compliance. Learn more by visiting our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

© 2020 Persopo.com. All Rights Reserved.
